// In this file you can specify the trial data for your experiment

//This might need to be changed, if we want to counter balanced between Decision and imagination,
//I don't think imagination needs to be counter balanced or does it?


const trial_info = {
    forced_choice_1_german: [
        {
            question: "Würdest du den Mann stoßen?",
            optionLeft: 'definitiv stoßen',
            optionRight: 'definitiv nicht stoßen'
        },
        {
            question: "Wie lebhaft stellst du dir den Mann vor?",
            optionLeft: "absolut klar",
            optionRight: "kein Bild"
        },
        {
            question: "Wie lebhaft stellst du dir die fünf Menschen vor?",
            optionLeft: "absolut klar",
            optionRight: "kein Bild"
        },
        {
            question: "Wie lebhaft stellst du dir die gesamte Situation vor?",
            optionLeft: "absolut klar",
            optionRight: "kein Bild"
        }
    ],
    forced_choice_2_german: [
        {
            question: "Was ist auf dem zweiten Brot?",
            option1: 'jam',
            option2: 'ham',
            correct: 'jam'
        },
        {
            question: "Wie ist das Wetter?",
            option1: "shiny",
            option2: "rainbow",
            correct: "shiny"
        }
    ],
    forced_choice_3_german: [
        {
            question: "Was ist auf dem dritten Brot?",
            option1: 'jam',
            option2: 'ham',
            correct: 'jam'
        },
        {
            question: "Wie ist das Wetter?",
            option1: "shiny",
            option2: "rainbow",
            correct: "shiny"
        }
    ],
    forced_choice_1_english: [
        {
            question: "Would you push the man?",
            optionLeft: 'definitely would not push him',
            optionRight: 'definitely would push him'
        },
        {
            question: "How vividly can you picture this scene?",
            optionLeft: "no image",
            optionRight: "very clear"
        }
    ],
    forced_choice_2_english: [
        {
            question: "What's on the second bread?",
            option1: 'jam',
            option2: 'ham',
            correct: 'jam'
        },
        {
            question: "How is the weather?",
            option1: "shiny",
            option2: "rainbow",
            correct: "shiny"
        }
    ],
    forced_choice_3_english: [
        {
            question: "What's on the third bread?",
            option1: 'jam',
            option2: 'ham',
            correct: 'jam'
        },
        {
            question: "How is the weather?",
            option1: "shiny",
            option2: "rainbow",
            correct: "shiny"
        }
    ]
};
